// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following type of class allows only one object of it to be created?",
        answer: "Singleton class",
        options: [
            "Virtual class",
            "Abstract class",
            "Friend class",
            "Singleton class"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How many instances of an abstract class can be created?",
        answer: "0",
        options: [
            "5",
            "3",
            "0",
            "1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following cannot be friend?",
        answer: "Object",
        options: [
            "Class",
            "Object",
            "Function",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Find average of natural numbers from 1 to 65?",
        answer: "33",
        options: [
            "33",
            "35",
            "32",
            "32.5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following two ratios is greater 17:18 and 10:11?",
        answer: "17:18",
        options: [
            "10:11",
            "Both are same",
            "17:18",
            "Cannot determine"
        ]
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Ram is three times as old as his Sam. 2 years ago he was five times as old as Sam. What is the present age of Ram?",
      answer: "12 years",
      options: [
        "12 years",
        "10 years",
        "14 years",
        "18 years"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "A person crosses a 600 m long street in 5 minutes. What is his speed in km per hour?",
        answer: "7.2",
        options: [
          "3.6",
          "7.2",
          "8.4",
          "10.0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Y has to score 40% marks to pass. He gets 20 marks and fails by 40 marks. The maximum marks of the exam are?",
        answer: "150",
        options: [
            "100",
            "120",
            "150",
            "200"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which one of the following is not a prime number?",
        answer: "91",
        options: [
            "31",
            "61",
            "71",
            "91"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "if log(a/b) + log(b/a) = log(a+b), then?",
        answer: "a + b = 1",
        options: [
            "a - b = 1",
            "a + b = 1",
            "a/b = 1",
            "a = b"
        ]
    },

];
